export const sampleDecks = [
    {
      id: '1',
      name: 'Basic French',
      language: 'French',
      cards: [
        { id: '1', front: 'Bonjour', back: 'Hello', memorized: false },
        { id: '2', front: 'Au revoir', back: 'Goodbye', memorized: false },
        { id: '3', front: 'Merci', back: 'Thank you', memorized: false },
        { id: '4', front: 'S\'il vous plaît', back: 'Please', memorized: false },
      ],
    },
    {
      id: '2',
      name: 'Basic Spanish',
      language: 'Spanish',
      cards: [
        { id: '1', front: 'Hola', back: 'Hello', memorized: false },
        { id: '2', front: 'Adiós', back: 'Goodbye', memorized: false },
        { id: '3', front: 'Gracias', back: 'Thank you', memorized: false },
        { id: '4', front: 'Por favor', back: 'Please', memorized: false },
      ],
    },
    {
      id: '3',
      name: 'Basic German',
      language: 'German',
      cards: [
        { id: '1', front: 'Guten Morgen', back: 'Good Morning', memorized: false },
        { id: '2', front: 'Guten Tag', back: 'Good Afternoon', memorized: false },
        { id: '3', front: 'Tschuss', back: 'Bye', memorized: false },
        { id: '4', front: 'Danke', back: 'Thank you', memorized: false },
      ],
    },
    {
      id: '4',
      name: 'Basic Japanese',
      language: 'Japanese',
      cards: [
        { id: '1', front: 'Konichiwa', back: 'Hello', memorized: false },
        { id: '2', front: 'Mizu', back: 'Water', memorized: false },
        { id: '3', front: 'Kudasai', back: 'Please', memorized: false },
        { id: '4', front: 'arigato', back: 'Thank you', memorized: false },
      ],
    },
  ];